[{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980696519,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":30290,"timeElapsed":124186},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980701776,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":5256,"timeElapsed":129443},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980708351,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":6574,"timeElapsed":136018},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980752200,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":43848,"timeElapsed":179867},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980763294,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":11093,"timeElapsed":190961},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980770187,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":6892,"timeElapsed":197854},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980777654,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":7467,"timeElapsed":205321},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980784370,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":6715,"timeElapsed":212037},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980787234,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":2863,"timeElapsed":214901},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980815940,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":26718,"timeElapsed":243607},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980818804,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":2864,"timeElapsed":246471},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980822034,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3228,"timeElapsed":249701},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980828825,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":6790,"timeElapsed":256492},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980831371,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2546,"timeElapsed":259038},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980834371,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2999,"timeElapsed":262038},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980837090,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2718,"timeElapsed":264757},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980840098,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":3006,"timeElapsed":267765},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980842464,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2365,"timeElapsed":270131},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980885713,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"246","question":"Do you use social media sites or apps? If so, which ones and why? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":41205,"timeElapsed":313380},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980888418,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"246","question":"Do you use social media sites or apps? If so, which ones and why? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":2704,"timeElapsed":316085},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980901159,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"246","question":"Do you use social media sites or apps? If so, which ones and why? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":12740,"timeElapsed":328826},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980908433,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"246","question":"Do you use social media sites or apps? If so, which ones and why? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":7273,"timeElapsed":336100},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980911491,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"246","question":"Do you use social media sites or apps? If so, which ones and why? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":3057,"timeElapsed":339158},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980914089,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"246","question":"Do you use social media sites or apps? If so, which ones and why? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":2597,"timeElapsed":341756},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980918694,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"246","question":"Do you use social media sites or apps? If so, which ones and why? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":4605,"timeElapsed":346361},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980921097,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"246","question":"Do you use social media sites or apps? If so, which ones and why? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":2403,"timeElapsed":348764},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980923486,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"246","question":"Do you use social media sites or apps? If so, which ones and why? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":2388,"timeElapsed":351153},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980937871,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":12802,"timeElapsed":365538},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980941094,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":3222,"timeElapsed":368761},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980945021,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":3927,"timeElapsed":372688},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980947647,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":2625,"timeElapsed":375314},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980953446,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5798,"timeElapsed":381113},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980957557,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":4109,"timeElapsed":385223},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980959780,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":2222,"timeElapsed":387447},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980962234,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":2453,"timeElapsed":389901},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980965097,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":2863,"timeElapsed":392764},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980970905,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":5807,"timeElapsed":398572},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980979540,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":6993,"timeElapsed":407207},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980981828,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":2287,"timeElapsed":409495},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980984490,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":2662,"timeElapsed":412157},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980987865,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":3374,"timeElapsed":415532},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980990204,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2338,"timeElapsed":417871},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980992895,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2690,"timeElapsed":420562},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980995522,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2626,"timeElapsed":423189},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980999890,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":4367,"timeElapsed":427557},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981003543,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":3653,"timeElapsed":431210},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981020634,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"53","question":"What do you think makes somebody a good parent or caretaker?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":15464,"timeElapsed":448301},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981024126,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"53","question":"What do you think makes somebody a good parent or caretaker?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":3491,"timeElapsed":451793},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981028304,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"53","question":"What do you think makes somebody a good parent or caretaker?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":4178,"timeElapsed":455971},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981031191,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"53","question":"What do you think makes somebody a good parent or caretaker?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":2886,"timeElapsed":458858},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981033833,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"53","question":"What do you think makes somebody a good parent or caretaker?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":2641,"timeElapsed":461500},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981036588,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"53","question":"What do you think makes somebody a good parent or caretaker?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":2755,"timeElapsed":464255},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981039070,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"53","question":"What do you think makes somebody a good parent or caretaker?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":2481,"timeElapsed":466737},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981044562,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"53","question":"What do you think makes somebody a good parent or caretaker?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":5491,"timeElapsed":472229},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981051204,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"53","question":"What do you think makes somebody a good parent or caretaker?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":6641,"timeElapsed":478871},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981075951,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":9249,"timeElapsed":503617},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981078965,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":3014,"timeElapsed":506632},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981081605,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":2639,"timeElapsed":509272},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981096423,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":14817,"timeElapsed":524090},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981100102,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":3678,"timeElapsed":527768},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981102720,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":2618,"timeElapsed":530387},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981105036,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":2315,"timeElapsed":532703},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981110556,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5518,"timeElapsed":538222},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981113111,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":2554,"timeElapsed":540778},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981115478,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2367,"timeElapsed":543145},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981144523,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"164","question":"What is the last concert or performance you saw? Had you seen the band or performer before? Where?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":27447,"timeElapsed":572190},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981147358,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"164","question":"What is the last concert or performance you saw? Had you seen the band or performer before? Where?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":2834,"timeElapsed":575025},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981150545,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"164","question":"What is the last concert or performance you saw? Had you seen the band or performer before? Where?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":3187,"timeElapsed":578212},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981153711,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"164","question":"What is the last concert or performance you saw? Had you seen the band or performer before? Where?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":3165,"timeElapsed":581378},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981156682,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"164","question":"What is the last concert or performance you saw? Had you seen the band or performer before? Where?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":2971,"timeElapsed":584349},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981159461,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"164","question":"What is the last concert or performance you saw? Had you seen the band or performer before? Where?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":2778,"timeElapsed":587128},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981162713,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"164","question":"What is the last concert or performance you saw? Had you seen the band or performer before? Where?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":3252,"timeElapsed":590380},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981166331,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"164","question":"What is the last concert or performance you saw? Had you seen the band or performer before? Where?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":3618,"timeElapsed":593998},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981168606,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"164","question":"What is the last concert or performance you saw? Had you seen the band or performer before? Where?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":2274,"timeElapsed":596273},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981177564,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"17","question":"What is your most treasured memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":7627,"timeElapsed":605231},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981180435,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"17","question":"What is your most treasured memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":2870,"timeElapsed":608102},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981183851,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"17","question":"What is your most treasured memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3415,"timeElapsed":611518},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981187110,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"17","question":"What is your most treasured memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":3259,"timeElapsed":614777},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981189959,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"17","question":"What is your most treasured memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":2848,"timeElapsed":617626},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981192671,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"17","question":"What is your most treasured memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":2712,"timeElapsed":620338},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981195484,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"17","question":"What is your most treasured memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":2812,"timeElapsed":623151},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981197981,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"17","question":"What is your most treasured memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":2496,"timeElapsed":625648},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981200650,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"17","question":"What is your most treasured memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":2668,"timeElapsed":628317},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981235342,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"223","question":"What is the most unusual food you’ve ever eaten? Describe where and when you last had this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":32922,"timeElapsed":663009},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981237861,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"223","question":"What is the most unusual food you’ve ever eaten? Describe where and when you last had this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":2518,"timeElapsed":665528},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981240200,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"223","question":"What is the most unusual food you’ve ever eaten? Describe where and when you last had this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":2339,"timeElapsed":667867},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981243194,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"223","question":"What is the most unusual food you’ve ever eaten? Describe where and when you last had this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":2993,"timeElapsed":670860},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981246036,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"223","question":"What is the most unusual food you’ve ever eaten? Describe where and when you last had this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":2842,"timeElapsed":673703},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981248339,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"223","question":"What is the most unusual food you’ve ever eaten? Describe where and when you last had this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":2302,"timeElapsed":676006},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981250732,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"223","question":"What is the most unusual food you’ve ever eaten? Describe where and when you last had this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":2393,"timeElapsed":678399},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981256843,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"223","question":"What is the most unusual food you’ve ever eaten? Describe where and when you last had this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":6110,"timeElapsed":684510},{"subjectID":"gnnmj8aush","prolificID":"672ca2646b6c51429825766f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24498096ab19bebbb2c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981259247,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"223","question":"What is the most unusual food you’ve ever eaten? Describe where and when you last had this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":2403,"timeElapsed":686914}]